{
    "subject": "resource/Marie-Magdeleine",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:1873_compositions",
    "human_readable": "Marie-Magdeleine is a subject of 1873 compositions.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7717174887657166,
            "question": "Who might have created these compositions about Marie-Magdeleine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7678431272506714,
            "question": "Who is Marie-Magdeleine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.75300133228302,
            "question": "What can these compositions tell us about Marie-Magdeleine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7522571682929993,
            "question": "What year were the compositions about Marie-Magdeleine created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.733069121837616,
            "question": "Can you name any of the compositions about Marie-Magdeleine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7281704545021057,
            "question": "How many compositions are associated with Marie-Magdeleine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7149359583854675,
            "question": "Where might we find these compositions about Marie-Magdeleine?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2526248097419739,
            "question": "What is the significance of these compositions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21466946601867676,
            "question": "What type of works are these compositions?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16527990996837616,
            "question": "Are there any themes common to these compositions?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Marie-Magdeleine is a subject of 1873 compositions.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2547_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of works are these compositions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2547_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of these compositions?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2547_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where might we find these compositions about Marie-Magdeleine?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2547_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2547_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2547_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2547_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2547_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2547_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2547_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2547_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2547_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2547_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2547_94.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states: \u201cMarie Magdeleine\u201d is a three-act, four-part oratorio first performed at the Odean Theatre in Paris on Good Friday 1873.  This confirms that Marie-Magdeleine was a subject of compositions in 1873. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided supports that \"Marie-Magdeleine\" is indeed a subject of compositions from 1873. The context mentions that the oratorio \"Marie Magdeleine\" by Jules Massenet was first performed in 1873, which aligns with the query."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}